A Guide to the General Records File of the University Relations Office of Information Services (William H. Wranek, Jr.), 1937-1949
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
General Records File of the University Relations Office of Information Services William H. Wranek, Jr. 1937-1949
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-4/2/6.491
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the University Library on 1976 December 12.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of the General Records File of the University Relations Office of Information Services.
Contents List
- American College Publicity Association Membership Report 1942 (Box 1)
- American College Publicity Association--Annual Report on Membership and Business Manager, etc. 1942 (Box 1)
- American College Public Relations Association 1947 Feb 1 (Box 1)
- Public Information Tips from the Department of Public Information--American Cancer Society 1947 Feb (Box 1)
- University of Virginia Geography Institute ca. 1947-1948 (Box 1)
- Virginia Music Festival--Duty Assignment Book 1948 Jun (Box 1)
- Class of 1948--Survey of Attendance 1948 (Box 1)
- Class of 1948--Degree Applicants 1948 (Box 1)
- American Cancer Society Publications 1948-1949 (Box 1)
- Oak Ridge Institute of Nuclear Studies--Press Release 1949 Feb 14 (Box 1)
- Magazine-- Pageant: Virginia Revolution 1949 Apr (Box 1)
- State-wide Conference of the High School Principals of Virginia 1949 Jun 20-23 (Box 1)
- Richmond Times-Dispatch article-- Tour to Benefit Restoration at the University: Pictures of the University 1949 Apr 24 (Box 1)
- News Release on Politically Independent Coalition [1950] Jan 19 (Box 1)
- Miscellaneous pamphlets re: publicity of United Nations ca. 1952 (Box 1)
- Miscellaneous-- Notes on Lecturers, etc. 1956 Mar 9 (Box 1)
- University of Virginia-- Pontiac's Varsity Show 1937 Oct 22 (Box 1)
- play: Knowledge in Action, Script # 65, Program # 65 n.d. (Box 1)
- Proposed Out-line of Virginia Institute of Highway Research n.d. (Box 1)
- Restoration of Shadwell would make Shrine of Jefferson's Birthplace n.d. (Box 1)
- Routine for Faculty-News Collector n.d. (Box 1)
- Suggested Reorganization of the College Curriculum at the University n.d. (Box 1)
- Virginia Players n.d. (Box 1)
- American National Theater and Academy n.d. (Box 1)
- The Detroit Symphony Orchestra --It's History n.d. (Box 1)
- Impact of War on Public Relations n.d. (Box 1)
- Miscellaneous Papers n.d. (Box 1)
- New Dominion Series n.d. (Box 1)
- Personal Autograph of Virginius Shackelford n.d. (Box 1)
- Public Relations in State Colleges and Universities n.d. (Box 1)
- Newsletter: Foreign Committee of Hamburg University n.d. (Box 1)
- Certificate of Honorable Discharge, Volunteer Training Unit (One autographed by President Newcomb) n.d. (Box 1)
- Additions to Faculty, 1948-1949 1948 (Box 1)